Guide to the Dave Martin Photographs of Male Nudes
Department of Special Collections
- Mixed athletes: caucasian and black athletes, 1951-1974, Series 3
  - Jack Alexander, 1955, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Mike Alvarez, 1956, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Brian Benson, n.d., 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Scott Carpenter, 1966, 4 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Joseph Carroll, 1965, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Justin Delaney, 1964, 4 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Bill Derrick, 1956, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Craig Dickson, Stanford University athlete, 1969, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Tim Evans, 1956, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Tony Farrell, 1952, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Joe Green, 1964, 3 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - John Harlan, Stanford University athlete, 1955, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Ray Harper, 1955, 5 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Jay Holt, 1965, 7 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Tommy Johnson, 1955, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Jeff Leonard, 1973, 7 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - John Manning, 1966, 10 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Terry Marcelus, 1974, 4 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Ron McNeal, 1955, 7 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Chuck Miller, 1953, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - John Newton, 1955, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Larry O'Brien, 1953, 3 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Virgil Owens, 1965, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Mark Peterson, 1966, 8 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Fred Reynolds, 1972, 6 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Richard Rose, U.C. Berkeley, 1971, 6 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - John Silva, 1964, 6 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Dave St. Denis, 1969, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Brent Stevens, 1955, 3 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Back poses, 1951-1974, Series 4
  - Sandy Alcorn, 1955, 4 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Mike Alvarez, 1956, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Brian Benson, n.d., 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Bob Bethea, 1955, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Greg Bradford, 1955, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Gary Brandon, Stanford University athlete, 1965, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Larry Briggs, U.C. Berkeley, 1966, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Scott Carpenter, 1966, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Ben Carter, 1965, 4 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Steve Clayton, 1965, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Larry Crawford, 1965, 3 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Rick Dayton, Stanford University athlete, 1969, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Gary Dexter, 1953, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Craig Dickson, Stanford University athlete, 1969, 5 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Bill Edwards, 1965, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Jim Elliott, U.C. Berkeley athlete, 1968, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Jim Ferguson, Stanford University athlete, 1973, 3 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - John Gledhill, 1968, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Cliff Harris, Stanford University athlete, 1968, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Tim Hogan, 1966, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Jay Holt, 1965, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Mike Jones, Stanford University athlete, 1954, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Lance Kendrick, 1965, 5 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Tyler Livingston, 1968, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Cliff Lopez, n.d., 4 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - John Manning, 1966, 3 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Terry Marcellus, 1974, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Fred Martinez, 1966, 3 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Charlie Masch, Stanford University athlete, 1973, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - John Mason, U.C. Berkeley athlete, 1965, 3 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Jay Miller, Stanford University athlete, n.d., 3 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Brad Payne, 1953, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Steve Radd, 1971, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Paul Ramirez, 1974, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Paul Revak, Stanford University athlete, 1955, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Tom Roan, 1972, 6 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Richard Rose, U.C. Berkeley athlete, 1971, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Rick Russell, 1969, 4 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Dave Sanchez, 1968, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Randy Saunders, 1969, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Mike Sill, 1956, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Dale Smith, 1956, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Phil St. James, U.C. Berkeley athlete, 1968, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Gene Stanley, 1953, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Lee Stevenson, Stanford University athlete, 1965, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Perry Stevenson, 1965, 4 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Wayne Stribling, 1966, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Jody Sutherland, U.C. Berkeley athlete, 1968, 3 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Bob Thomas, 1968, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Charlie Wall, 1968, 2 photographs: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Jim Warren, U.C. Berkeley athlete, 1953, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Tom West, 1965, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Dick Woodward, 1956, 1 photograph: b&w; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 20, Folder 53)
- Index to photographs, 1951-1974, Series 5
  - Photographic index to models, Alcorn to Christopher (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Photographic index to models, Connor to Johnson (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Photographic index to models, Jones to Peterson (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Photographic index to models, Reed to Sutherland (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Photographic index to models, Swift to York (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Photographs by others, 1951-1974, Series 6
  - Douglas Juleff (1919-2000), known as "Douglas of Detroit". Vic Seipke, Detroit Fireman, 1950s, 17 prints (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Douglas Juleff (1919-2000), known as "Douglas of Detroit". Stan Stanczyk, Polish weightlifter, Detroit, Michigan, 1946, 14 prints (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - The Ritter Brothers: Fred and William of Astoria, Long Island, New York, ca. 1935, 11 prints (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Tony Sansone, ca. 1936 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Biographical information, 1980-2004, Series 7
  - Biographies of Dave Martin, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Biographies of Dave Martin printed from Dave Martin website, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Research material, 1951-1974, Series 8
  - Male physique photographers, 1920s through 1970s / by Dave Martin, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - John M. Hernic: the father of physique photography, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Classic magazine covers: originals [1 of 2], n.d. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Classic magazine covers: originals [2 of 2], n.d. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Classic magazine covers: color photocopies, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Histories of nude male photography, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Bay Area photographs, 1951-1974, Series 9
  - Coit Tower, 1952, 2 photographs: b&w; 51 x 41 cm. (Othertype 24)
  - Golden Gate Bridge: aerial views, 1952, 2 photographs: b&w; 51 x 41 cm. (Othertype 24)
  - The trees at the base of Coit Tower, 1952, 1 photograph: b&w; 51 x 41 cm. (Othertype 24)
  - Vista thru the trees on the hill across from the Cliff House Restaurant, 1952, 1 photograph: b&w; 51 x 41 cm. (Othertype 24)
  - Downtown Oakland, 1952, 1 photograph: b&w; 51 x 41 cm. (Othertype 24)
  - Golden Gate Bridge in the fog, 1952, 1 photographs: b&w; 51 x 41 cm. (Othertype 24)